<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetadata xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Name>Re-Volt [StationeersMods]</Name>
  <Author>Sukasa</Author>
  <Version>1.1.0</Version>
  <!-- Steam description using steam styling tags for Steam workshop page -->
  <Description>
    [b]WARNING:[/b] This is a StationeersLaunchPad Plugin Mod. It requires Bepinex to be installed with the StationeersLaunchPad plugin.
    See: https://github.com/StationeersLaunchPad/StationeersLaunchPad

    [h1]⚡ Re-Volt ⚡[/h1]

    Re-Volt is an electrical overhaul mod for Stationeers, which mildly overhauls how power is distributed, what happens when things go wrong, and gives you more tools to control your power!

    [h2]🔌 Features[/h2]

    [b]Electrical load is now proportionally shared among all sources on a cable network![/b]  No longer will you have to deal with one battery draining while the others are completely full!

    [b]Wires no longer burn out instantly![/b]  Instead, wires will burn out with a random chance, based on how much you're overloading them.  It never made sense that a cable which could carry 5,000 watts continuously would violently rupture in half a second when carrying 5,001 watts.  And now it doesn't.

    [b]Stationary batteries are now charge- and discharge-rate limited.[/b]  A single battery isn't going to take 100kW anymore, and these babies can discharge a fair bit quicker than they charge.  You might need to re-design your power distribution, or use a few more batteries in parallel!

    [b]Fuses still work.[/b]  As long as there is a fuse rated low enough to protect the cable, that fuse will ALWAYS blow instead of a cable.  And fuses blow instantly, no time delay.

    [b]Complex/recursive electrical networks are allowed.[/b]  With the revised power simulation, the limit on transformers or batteries in recursive networks has been lifted.  Over-engineer your bases to your heart's delight!.

    [h2]📅 Future Plans[/h2]

    In future, there are a few more components planned out:
    [list]
    [*] Either reversed small breakers, or [b]bi-directional breakers[/b].  I'm not sure which, yet.
    [*] Heavy Breakers, capable of interrupting much larger amounts of power
    [*] Smart variants of both, able to be monitored and controlled over the data network!
    [/list]

    [h1]🧾 Credits[/h1]

    Nothing is ever born in a vacuum, and neither was this mod.  HUGE thanks to a number of folks in the Stationeers Modding Discord, and of course to Rocketwerkz for just being as awesome as they are.

    [h2]🆘 Need Support?[/h2]

    If you need support, you can reach out here or on the Stationeers Modding Discord, in the Re-Volt project post, or on the Github repository at https://github.com/sukasa/revolt

  </Description>
  
  <!-- Ingame Description using TMP tags for Workshop menu -->
  <InGameDescription>
    <![CDATA[<size="30"><color=#ffa500> ReVolt </color></size>
<b>WARNING:</b> <color=#ff0000>This is a StationeersLaunchPad Plugin Mod. It requires Bepinex to be installed with the StationeersLaunchPad plugin.</color>
See: https://github.com/StationeersLaunchPad/StationeersLaunchPad
Re-Volt is an electrical overhaul mod for Stationeers, which mildly overhauls how power is distributed, what happens when things go wrong, and gives you more tools to control your power!
    [b]The entire electrical simulation has been rewritten.[/b]  Electrical load is now proportionally shared among all sources on a cable network.

    [b]Wires no longer burn out instantly![/b]  Wires will burn out with a random chance, based on how much you're overloading them.

    [b]Stationary batteries are now charge- and discharge-rate limited.[/b]

    [b]Fuses still work.[/b]

    [b]Recursive electrical networks are allowed[/b]
]]>
  </InGameDescription>
  <!-- All contents of ChangeLog should be changed for each publication for Steam workshop page -->
  <ChangeLog>
    [h3]Version 1.1.0:[/h3]
    [list]
    [*]The initial public release of Re-Volt!
    [*]Adds the main power simulation rewrite as well as the first Small Breaker prefab.  A reversed Small Breaker may come later.
    [/list]
  </ChangeLog>
  <!-- StationeersLaunchPad and BepInEx tags for Steam workshop page will be automatically added by the framework when publishing -->
  <Tags>
    <Tag>StationeersLaunchPad</Tag>
  </Tags>
  <!-- Automatic downloads of dependencies -->
  <Dependencies />
  <!-- Automatic reordering of the mods list -->
  <LoadBefore />
  <LoadAfter />
</ModMetadata>
