<ModMetadata xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Name>Re-Volt</Name>
  <Author>Sukasa</Author>
  <Version>1.7.6</Version>
  <!-- Steam description using steam styling tags for Steam workshop page -->
  <Description>
    [h1]⚡ Re-Volt ⚡[/h1]

    Re-Volt is an electrical overhaul mod for Stationeers, which mildly overhauls how power is distributed, what happens when things go wrong, and gives you more tools to control your power!

    [b]WARNING:[/b]This is an SLP Plugin Mod, ensure you have it installed!
    
    [h2]🔌 Features[/h2]

    [b]NEW! Optoisolator and Data Diode:[/b] Connect data networks together while keeping power separate.  The Optoisolator is a 4-network bidirectional link, and the Data Diode is a two network one-way link
    
    [b]Cable Tray:[/b] Why spend a ton of space keeping all those cables separate?  With a Cable Tray, you can run many different cables together through a tray, taking up less space and fewer objects.  Trays connect cables with matching colour and watt limits.
    
    [b]Load Centers![/b]  With the new Load Center structure, you can control entire sets of devices without needing a separate power network.  Turn your lights, atmospherics, doors, equipment, or logic devices on and off en masse - and also supports data networking, with a secondary data port.

    [b]Electrical load is now proportionally shared among all sources on a cable network![/b]  No longer will you have to deal with one battery draining while the others are completely full!  And even better, this goes the same for charging them.  One battery won't hog all the power!

    [b]Wires no longer burn out instantly![/b]  Instead, wires will burn out with a random chance, based on how much you're overloading them.  It never made sense that a cable which could carry 5,000 watts continuously would violently rupture in half a second when carrying 5,001 watts.  And now it doesn't.

    [b]Stationary batteries are now charge- and discharge-rate limited.[/b]  A single battery isn't going to take 100kW anymore, and these babies can discharge a fair bit quicker than they charge.  You might need to re-design your power distribution, or use a few more batteries in parallel!

    [b]Circuit Breakers![/b]  Like fuses, with a greater degree of control over the specific trip point - and which, after tripping, can be reset without having to build a new fuse.  These can also protect your wires if you get sudden surges of power...

    [b]Smart Breakers![/b]  If you wanted more information about what your breakers are doing, or need the instant trip?  Smart Breakers are your solution.
    
    [b]Heavy Breakers![/b]  When 5kW isn't enough, the Heavy Breaker steps in.  Supporting up to a 500kW trip point, the Heavy Breaker can handle any load.  Plus, Heavy Breakers can form modular switchgear!

    [b]Fuses still work.[/b]  As long as there is a fuse rated low enough to protect the cable, that fuse will ALWAYS blow instead of a cable.  And fuses blow instantly, no time delay.

    [b]Complex/recursive electrical networks are allowed.[/b]  With the revised power simulation, the limit on transformers or batteries in recursive networks has been lifted.  Over-engineer your bases to your heart's delight!  Also, transformers are less exploitable now - but take note, they (and APCs) also properly apply their own power requirements to the upstream!

    [b]T-Ray Scanners:[/b] The T-Ray scanner bug where some cables/etc would not display is fixed, and Cable Tray also appears on the scanner
    
    [h2]📅 Future Plans[/h2]

    There's still more content on the way:
    [list]
    [*] Bug fixes, maintenance, and possibly more components in future!
    [/list]

    [h1]🧾 Credits[/h1]

    Nothing is ever born in a vacuum, and neither was this mod.  HUGE thanks to a number of folks in the Stationeers Modding Discord, and of course to Rocketwerkz for just being as awesome as they are.

    [h2]🆘 Need Support?[/h2]

    If you need support, you can reach out here or on the Stationeers Modding Discord, in the Re-Volt project post, or on the GitHub repository at https://github.com/sukasa/revolt

  </Description>
  <!-- In-game Description using TMP tags for Workshop menu -->
  <InGameDescription><![CDATA[<color=#ff0000>This is an SLP Plugin Mod, ensure you have it installed!</color>
    <size="30"><color=#ffa500>Re-Volt</color></size>
    Re-Volt is THE electrical overhaul mod for Stationeers, reworking power and cable mechanics and adding useful tools.
    <b>Electrical simulation:</b>  Electrical load is now proportionally shared among all sources and split fairly between all loads.
    <b>Wire Burnout:</b>  Wires burn out after overload, but not instantly.
    <b>Stationary batteries are now charge- and discharge-rate limited.</b>
    <b>Fuses still work.</b>  They provide absolute protection.  Once.
    <b>Recursive networks:</b> Now allowed!  With a side of exploit fixes!
    <b>Breakers & Cable Tray:</b> Circuit Breakers, Switchgear, and Cable Tray!  Oh my!
    <b>Data Networking:</b> Optoisolators and Data Diodes to connect data networks!
]]></InGameDescription>
  <!-- All contents of ChangeLog should be changed for each publication for Steam workshop page -->
  <ChangeLog>
    [h3]Version 1.7.6[/h3]
    [list]
    [*] Cable Trays better handle cable colours changing during gameplay
    [/list]
  </ChangeLog>
  <WorkshopHandle>3587239682</WorkshopHandle>
  <!-- StationeersLaunchPad and BepInEx tags for Steam workshop page will be automatically added by the framework when publishing -->
  <Tags>
    <Tag>StationeersLaunchPad</Tag>
  </Tags>
  <!-- Automatic downloads of dependencies -->
  <Dependencies>
    <Mod>
      <Id>3751750326</Id>
    </Mod>
  </Dependencies>
  <!-- Automatic reordering of the mods list -->
  <LoadBefore />
  <LoadAfter />
</ModMetadata>